<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Upkeep-app</string>
    <string name="fleets">Fleets</string>
    <string name="boats">Boats</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="components">Components</string>
    <string name="upkeeps">Upkeeps</string>
    <string name="tasks">Tasks</string>
    <string name="stores">Stores</string>
    <string name="users">Users</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="views">Views</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="delete_all">Delete all</string>
    <string name="change_user_type">Change user type</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="owner">Owner</string>
    <string name="wrong_data">Wrong data</string>
    <string name="code">Code</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="fleet">Fleet</string>
    <string name="boat">Boat</string>
    <string name="brand">Brand</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="serialNumber">Serial number</string>
    <string name="observations">Observations</string>
    <string name="service">Service</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="component">Component</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="length">Length</string>
    <string name="operator">Operator</string>
    <string name="upkeep">Upkeep</string>
    <string name="minStock">Minimum stock</string>
    <string name="numStock">Stock</string>
    <string name="task">Task</string>
    <string name="terms0">Terms of license and privacy policy</string>
    <string name="terms1">By checking the box and clicking continue, you agree to the </string>
    <string name="terms2">license terms and privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="terms3">Terms, conditions and PRIVACY POLICY Updated on 2022-05-24</string>
    <string name="terms4">General terms</string>
    <string name="terms5">This Privacy Policy establishes the terms in which Upkeep-app uses and protects the information that is provided by its users at the time of use. This company is committed to the security of its users\' data. When we ask you to fill in the personal information fields with which you can be identified, we do so by ensuring that it will only be used in accordance with the terms of this document. However, this Privacy Policy may change over time or be updated, so we recommend and emphasize that you continually review this page to ensure that you agree with such changes. By accessing or using our Service, you indicate that you have read, understand, and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="terms6">Information that is collected</string>
    <string name="terms7">We collect information from you when you visit our platform, register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.</string>
    <string name="terms8">Name / username</string>
    <string name="terms9">Emails</string>
    <string name="terms10">job titles</string>
    <string name="terms11">Password</string>
    <string name="terms12">Use of the information collected</string>
    <string name="terms13">Our app uses the information in order to provide the best possible service, particularly to keep track of users, purchases if applicable, and improve our products and services. It is possible that emails are sent periodically through our app with special offers, new products and other advertising information that we consider relevant to you or that may provide you with some benefit, these emails will be sent to the address you provide and may be canceled At any time.</string>
    <string name="terms14">Upkeep-app is highly committed to fulfilling the commitment to keep your information safe. We use the most advanced systems and constantly update them to ensure that there is no unauthorized access.</string>
    <string name="terms15">Governing Law</string>
    <string name="terms16">This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of Spain without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in connection with any action or dispute arising between the parties under or in connection with this Privacy Policy, except for those persons who may be entitled to bring claims under the Privacy Shield or the Swiss-US mark.</string>
    <string name="terms17">The laws of Spain, excluding its conflicts of laws, will govern this Agreement and your use of the platform. Your use of the Platform may also be subject to other local, state, national or international laws.</string>
    <string name="terms18">By using Upkeep-app or contacting us directly, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not interact with our website or use our services. Your continued use of the Website, direct interaction with us, or following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy that do not materially affect the use or disclosure of your personal information will mean you accept those changes.</string>
    <string name="terms19">    Third Party Links</string>
    <string name="terms20">This website may contain links to other sites that may be of interest to you. Once you click on these links and leave our page, we no longer have control over the site to which you are redirected and therefore we are not responsible for the terms or privacy or the protection of your data on those other third party sites. These sites are subject to their own privacy policies, so it is recommended that you consult them to confirm that you agree with them.</string>
    <string name="terms21">Control of your personal information</string>
    <string name="terms22">At any time you can restrict the collection or use of personal information that is provided to our app. Every time you are asked to fill in a form, such as the user registration form, you can check or uncheck the option to receive information by email. If you have marked the option to receive our newsletter or advertising, you can cancel it at any time.</string>
    <string name="terms23">This company will not sell, assign or distribute personal information that is collected without your consent, unless required by a judge with a court order.</string>
    <string name="terms24">Upkeep-app reserves the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time.</string>
    <string name="terms25">Block and disable Cookies and similar technologies</string>
    <string name="terms26">Wherever you are located, you can also set your browser to block cookies and similar technologies, but this may block our essential cookies and prevent our website from working properly, and you may not be able to fully use all of its features and services. You should also note that you may also lose saved information (eg saved login details, site preferences) if you block cookies in your browser. Different browsers make different controls available to you. Disabling a cookie or a cookie category does not delete the cookie from your browser, you will have to do it yourself from your browser, you should visit the help menu of your browser for more information.</string>
    <string name="terms27">Children\'s Privacy</string>
    <string name="terms28">We do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.</string>
    <string name="terms29">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="terms30">Feel free to contact us if you have any questions.</string>
    <string name="terms31">Via email: braisfv22@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="continueText">Continue</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="must_accept">You must accept the terms and conditions to continue</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="identification">Identification</string>
    <string name="surnames">Surnames</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="recent">Recent</string>
    <string name="profile_data">Profile data</string>
    <string name="logout">Log out</string>
</resources>